Mishaps. Misadventures. Mayhem. Oh joy.
Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events is a adventure,
comedy, family film directed by Brad Silberling.
Three wealthy children's parents are killed in a fire.
When they are sent to a distant relative, they find out that he
is plotting to kill them and seize their fortune.
Violet Baudelaire, played by Emily Browning.
Klaus Baudelaire, played by Liam Aiken.
Sunny Baudelaire, played by Kara Hoffman.
Sunny Baudelaire, played by Shelby Hoffman.
Count Olaf / Dr. Stephano / Captain Sham, played by Jim Carrey.
Josephine Anwhistle, played by Meryl Streep.
Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events is a 2004
action-adventure game based on the film of the same name.
Players take the roles of Violet, Klaus, and Sunny Baudelaire,
solving puzzles, fighting villains and finding objects.
Players encounter characters such as Mr.
Poe, Uncle Monty, and Aunt Josephine, along with villains such as Count Olaf, the
Hook-Handed Man, the White-Faced Women, and the Bald Man with the Long Nose.
Jim Carrey, Emily Browning, and Liam Aiken reprise their roles from the film, while the voice of Lemony
Snicket is provided by Tim Curry, who provided narration for the audiobooks for the series.
The film explores themes of steampunk, orphan, orphan
siblings, unfortunate, based on young adult novel.
The tone is lighthearted.